In the table leg extension, the table posture itself, is very good for strengthening back and shoulders and arms but the leg extension is going to bring it in for your lower back, connecting it all the way to the shoulders.
You take the hands right down into the floor and when you do this, you take both feet in the floor, and you're going to lift yourself up.
Many people can only take their hips off the floor, just a little bit, because they feel the pressure inside their shoulders and arms.
You can build that resistance by taking slow steps into this posture.
If you can, lift your belly right up and rest your head right back.
Take a deep breath in and lift that right leg straight out and then exhale.
Bring it down and touch the floor.
Inhale, left leg goes out and exhale, come down, keeping your belly up.
Inhale and exhale.
Inhale, exhale, inhale and exhale.
One more time, right and left.
Inhale and exhale and inhale and exhale, release.
Come right down.